

# Javad Rajabzade

Software Engineer

#### **About Me**

Hello! I'm Javad Rajabzade. Software Engineer, Back-end, Microservice programming and UI/UX design are some of my specialties. An expert in Graphic Design tools like Photoshop and Adobe XD, I am a skilled Back-end Developer.

Age 28

Email dev@javad.tech

Phone +98935-773-8933

Phone 2 +98910-659-5127

#### **Professional Skills**

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

**JavaScript** 



## **Work Experience**

## Software Engineer at Mawson INC

Apr, 2021 - Now

Knowledge of the Filecoin network and implementation of the Filecoin Lotus optimisation

# Back-end Developer at Wzor Group < twitter.com/WZorNET

Sep, 2009 - Now

KMS Emulator service design with ratiborus58, MPK (Microsoft product key share service), PID Key Checker 3.0.0

### Back-end Developer and Graphic Designer at

MoeinSoft < moeinsoft.com >

Nov, 2017 - Apr, 2021

Moein Accounting Software, Anti-Ransomware Moein, MoeinBackup develop, Setup Experience Devlop with InstallAware, Linux administration

### **Education**

#### Software technology engineering from Azad University

2018 - 2020

Software technology engineering knowledge about programming C Advanced Level, C++ Advanced Level, C#, assembly, Network programming , software engineering.

#### Associate Computer from Azad University

2016 - 2018

Knowledge about C, C#, VB.NET, Assembly basic, Network

#### **Contact**

#### **Address**

Floor 1, No 73, 20.4 Azadeh Street, Mashhad, Khorasan Razavi, Iran

#### **Phone**

- +98935-773-8933
- +98910-659-5127
- +98998-100-2701

#### **Email**

dev@javad.tech

ja7adr@gmail.com